Guide to The Peter Dougherty Collection 1965 - 2001 MSS.213
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Sound recordings, 242013
  - Subseries A: Audio Works, 1976-1985; 197226
    - Patti Smith Group + friends, March 9th 1977, David Johansen, Tapper Zukie, Iggy, Paley Bros., Elliot Randall, Dougherty - guitars, A. Paley - Drums, Eric Rosenfeld (Manhattan Ocean Club), March 9, 1977; ID: 213.0147; 198179 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0147, Case 213.0147_pt.1, Case 213.0147_pt.2)
      Container Annotation: X D. Johansen, () Tapper Zukie, [] Iggy, ^ Paley Bros, * Elliot Randall, @ Dougherty -g- vocal, A. Paley- drums, Eric Rosenfeld
    - Patti Smith Group - Live CBGBs, NYC 2 Jun '77 Basic Training III, June 2, 1977; ID: 213.0148; 198180 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0148, Case 213.0148)
      Side A (44:31) Hunter, Magellan, Under My Skin, Jailhouse Rock, Kimberly, Redendo Beach, Space Monkey, You Really Got Me, Jolene, Ask the Angels
      Side B (32:36) Time is on My Side, Radio Ethiopia, R'n'R Nigger, Pumpin', -encores-, Piss Factory, Gloria
      Container Annotation: Performance and all material copyright by Patti Smith Group/ 1977. All commercial rights retained. Cr0z Digital Stereo
    - Patti, Palladium, May 20, 1978, ID: 213.0149; 198181 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0149, Case 213.0149_pt.1, Case 213.0149_pt.2)
      Side A: RnR Nigger, Set Me Free, Victory, Kimberly, Space Monkey, Kids Are Alright, 26 Floor, [Track Unknown], Time is on My Side
      Side B: We Three, [Track Unknown]
    - Patti Smith Live March 22nd at CBGBs, Bleecker & Bowery, undated; ID: 213.0150; 198182 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0150, Case 213.0150)
      Side A: Piss Factory, Don't Take My Harp Away (From Me), (Patti Smith and Tom Verlaine), Green Money, Break it Up
      Side B: Land
      Patti Smith- vocals, Lenny Kaye- guitar. Prop. of P. Dougherty 212 544 9224
    - III Patti 76/77 Village Gate poetry, 1976/1977; ID: 213.0151; 198183 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0151, Case 213.0151_pt.1, Case 213.0151_pt.2)
      Side A: Fear of the BOC Reaper, Birdland, My Generation (Daniel J.), Sympathy for the Devil
      Side B: Marquee Moon[redaction], Will Hollywood Ever Learn, Neo Boy, Fire of Unknown Origin, Precious Little, Babble Field
    - New Year's Eve 76/77. Cale/ Patti Smith Group? [written over], December 31, 1976 - January 1, 1977; ID: 213.0152; 198184 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0152, Case 213.0152_pt.1, Case 213.0152_pt.2)
      Side A: Leaving it Up to You, Gun --> Pablo Picasso, Heartbreak Hotel, Waiting For My Man, Land of 1000 Dances, Ask the Angels, Redondo Beach, Free Money
      Side B: Dig, Space Monkey, Pissin' in the River, Pumpin', Ain't it Strange, 1977, (Dark Star), Land
    - P.S. [Patti Smith] Group, March 10th 77, March 10, 1977; ID: 213.0153; 198185 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0153, Case 213.0153)
      Gimme Some Lovin, The Kid, You Really Got Me, No [Jesterity]
    - Patti Smith, undated; ID: 213.0154; 198186 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0154, Case 213.0154)
    - Lou Reed - live at the Geneva Theatre 10/30/76, October 30, 1976; ID: 213.0155; 198187 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0155, Case 213.0155_pt.1, Case 213.0155_pt.1A, Case 213.0155_pt.2)
      Sides A: Sweet Jane, Good Time Music, Lisa Says, Kicks, She's My Best Friend, Waiting For My Man, Sheltered Life, They're Taking The Children Away, [Track Unknown], Vicious Circle, Coney Island Baby, RocknRoll Heart
      Side B: Charlie's Girl, Kill Your Sons, Satellite of Love, How Do You Think It Feels?, Temporary Thing, (encores-->) RocknRoll, Heroin, Sister Ray
      Tape Length: Part 1: 00:56:20; Part 2: 00:61:30
    - John Cale/Church & Anthrax, Vintage Violence. Recorded in Dolby 12/29/76, December 29, 1976; ID: 213.0156; 198188 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0156, Case 213.0156_pt.1, Case 213.0156_pt.2)
      Content
      Side A (Church & Anthrax): Church of Anthrax, The Hall of Mirrors in the Palace at Versailles, The Soul of Patrick Lee, Ides of March, The Protégé. Terry Riley, John Cale, Adam Miller
      Side B (Vintage Violence): Hello There, Gideon's Bible, Adelaine, Big White Cloud, Cleo, Please, Charlemagne, Bring It On Up, Amsterdam, Ghost Story, Fairweather Friend
      Container Annotation: Singles- Feel Good, Roxette, Keep It Out of Sight. Eddie & the Hot Rods- Wooly Bully, Horse Play.
    - John Cale- Paris 1919/ Academy in Peril, ID: 213.0157; 198189 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0157, Case 213.0157_pt.1, Case 213.0157_pt.2)
      Side A: PARIS 1919: Child's Christmas in Wales, Hanky Panky, Nohow, The Endless Plain of Fortune, Andalucia, Macbeth, Paris 1919, Graham Greene, Half Past France, Antarctica Starts Here. ACADEMY IN PERIL: The Philosopher, Brahms
      Side B: Legs Larry at Television Centre, The Academy in Peril, Intro: Days of Steam, 3 Orchestral Pieces: Faust, The Balance, Capt Morgan's Lament, King Harry, John Milton-- Sylvia Said.
      Container Annotation: Richie Hayward- drums, Lowell George- guitar, Ron Wood - Track 2, The Royal Philharmonic Orchestra - 6 & 8
    - Lou Reed Live at LOEWS Syracuse NY May 7 1975, ID: 213.0158; 198190 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0158, Case 213.0158)
      Content: 1- Sweet Jane, I Wanna Be Black, For The Coach, Glory of Love, Waiting for the Man, You Can Dance, How Do You Think It Feels?, Uptown Dirt. 2- Walk on the Wild Side, What's Your Style?, Complete Tthis Story Now, White Light
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1 and Part 2. [Part 2 contains end of ID# 213.0480: "Lou Reed 11/13/1976 Palladium"]
    - Dils Hurrah, June 18, 1979 - June 19, 1979; ID: 213.0159; 198191 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0159, Case 213.0159_pt.1, Case 213.0159_pt.2)
      Side A (June 18, 1979)
      Side B (June 19, 1979)
    - Velvets 6/26/70 Max's Rehearsal. Lou Reed '70, June 26, 1970; ID: 213.0160; 198192 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0160, Case 213.0160_pt.1, Case 213.0160_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: What Goes On?, Cool it Down, New Age, Walk it Talk it, Who Loves the Sun?, I'm so Free, Can't Stand it, Walk it Talk it, Ridin to the Sun, I'm Stickin to You, Lisa Says, Kill Your Sons, Lonely Sat Nite
    - Lou - Royal Festival Hall with Spiders/Shady Grove Maryland/Lou & Tots Imperial College London, 1972-1973; ID: 213.0161; 198193 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0161, Case 213.0161)
      Side A: White Light*, Waiting 4 My Man*, Sweet Jane*, Rock & Roll (), Sister Ray ()
      Side B: White Light, Lonesome Cowboy, Pale Blue Eyes
      Container Annotation: * Royal Festival Hall w/ Spiders, () Shady Grove Maryland June 1973, 21 Oct 72 Lou & Tots Imperial College
    - Lou Reed, Live Dec 26, 1972 Ultrasonic Studios, December 26, 1972; ID: 213.0162; 198194 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0162, Case 213.0162)
      Side A: White Light- White Heat, Vicious, Waiting for My Man, Walk It- TalkIt, Sweet Jane, Heroin
      Side B: Heroin (cont'd), Satellite of Love, Walk On The Wild Side, I'm So Free, Berlin, Rock 'n' Roll
    - Lou & the Tots 10/21/72 Imperial College, October 21, 1972; ID: 213.0163; 198195 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0163, Case 213.0163_pt.1, Case 213.0163_pt.2)
      Side A: White Light, Lonesome Cowboy Bill, Waiting [For] the Man, Pale Blue Eyes, I'll Be Your Mirror, Candy Says, Sweet Jane, Heroin
      Side B: Berlin, Who Loves the Sun, I Can't Stand It, Wild Child, Rock N Roll, Head Held High, Sister Ray, Miles End Sundown, Walk On The Wild Side
    - Velvet Underground Demos 65/66, 1965/1966; ID: 213.0164; 198196 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0164, Case 213.0164_pt.1, Case 213.0164_pt.2)
      Side A: Ostrich, Sneaky Pete, Sheltered Life, It's Alright, The Way You Live, I'm Not Sorry, Here She Comes Now, Inside of Your Heart, Caroline Says, One of These Days, Ocean
      Side B: Rock 'n' Roll, She's My Best Friend, Sticking to You, Foggy Notion, Ferryboat Bill, Andy's Chest, Drive Me Insane, Cycle Annie, Sister Ray
    - Lou Reed Live in Syracuse May 7 1975, ID: 213.0165; 198197 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0165)
      Content: Side A: 1. Sweet Jane, 2. I Wanna Be Black, 3. Football For the Coach, 4. Glory of Love (Coney Island Baby), 5. Waiting For My Man, 6. You Can Dance, 7. How Do You Think It Feels?, 8. Uptown Dirt, 9. Walk on the Wild Side. Side b: 10. What's Your Style? (Kicks), 11. Complete This Story Now, 12. White Light/ White Heat, 13. Rock and Roll. Sister Ray (cont'd). Lou Reed- vocal, guitar! Doug Yule- guitar, b. vocal. -sax. -bass. -drums. Loew's Theatre
    - Cale/ Roxy singles/ Patti Smith - Horses, undated; ID: 213.0166; 198198 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0166, Case 213.0166_pt.1, Case 213.0166_pt.2)
      Side A (CALE, Roxy B-Sides & Hot Singles) Helen of Troy, Guts, Heartbreak Hotel, The Ballad of Cable Hogue, Leaving It Up To You/(ROXY): Virginia, Plain the Number, Pajamarama, Pride of the Pain, [2 M. B.], Remake/Remodel, For Your Pleasure (live), Eno- The Lion Sleeps Tonight (cut)
      Container Annotation: Cale Nov 30th 1975 singles- [Alister] - P.D. (212)5449224.
      Side B (PATTI SMITH HORSES): Gloria, Redondo Beach, Birdland, Free Monday, Kimberly, Break It Up, Land, Elegie.
      Container Annotation: Vocal- Patti Smith, guitar- Lenny Kaye, Piano-Richard Sohl, Bass,Guitra - Ivan Kral
    - Erasers - May 16 & 28, 1977, CBGB, May 1977; ID: 213.0167; 198199 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0167, Case 213.0167)
      Side A: #7, Jody, Marc in Leather, Come Out in the Streets, I Don't Love Anyone, Everybody's Got a Dog, 1977-, Jody, No fun, Funtime, Come Out in the Streets
      Side B: Marc in Leather, Everybody's Got a Dog
    - John Cale & Friends, July 26, 27th 1976, July 26, 1976 - July 27, 1976; ID: 213.0168; 198200 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0168, Case 213.0168_pt.1, Case 213.0168_pt.2)
      Side A (July 26): Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Know, Guts, Waiting For the Man, Close Watch, [Track Unknown], Gun --> Pablo Picasso, Cable Hogue
      Side B: Babe What Ya Want Me To Do/ (July 27) Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Do, Darling, Guts, Waiting For My Man, Gun --> Pablo Picasso.
      Container Annotation: J. Cale- vocal, guitar, piano. P. Smith- vocal, guitar? D. Byrne- guitar. A. Lanier -piano, guitar, Mick Ronson - guitar
    - Nico BBC/ Paris 72, 1972; ID: 213.0169; 198201 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0169, Case 213.0169)
      Sides A and B: Secret Sides, [Transfer of Love], We've Got the Gold, the End, Pale Blue Eyes, Black Angel Death, Heroin
      Tape Length: Unknown
    - Lou Reed live Oct 6 1974, October 6, 1974; ID: 213.0170; 198202 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0170, Case 213.0170_pt.1, Case 213.0170_pt.2)
      Side A: Intro-Sweet Jane, Vicious, Ride Sally Ride, Heroin, Animal Talk, Sally Can't Dance, Walk on the Wild Side
      Side B: NY Stars, Kill Your Sons, White Light/ White Heat, [Gooden Mr. Cabe], Rock & Roll
    - Lou Reed, Dec 26 1972, December 26, 1972; ID: 213.0171; 198203 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0171, Case 213.0171)
    - [Lou Reed - R and R Heart Tour - Palladium, November 13, 1976], ID: 213.0480; 267886 (Box 3, Media ID: 213.0480, Case 213.0480_pt.1, Case 213.0480_pt.2)
      Format: CD
      Access CD available by appointment only. Please request Part 1 and Part 2. [Part 2 access CD begins with 213.0158 "Lou Reed Live at LOEWS Syracuse NY May 7 1975"]
    - Judy Nylon w/ Nolan, Ed/ Dead Boys w/ J. Nolan, May 3, 1978; ID: 213.0172; 198204 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0172, Case 213.0172_pt.1, Case 213.0172_pt.2)
      Side A: Trial by Fire, Whem I'm Bored, All I Want, Breakdown
      Side B: Time's Up Looking For a Kiss
    - John Cale & Friends July 26, 27 1976 Lower Manhattan Ocean Club, July 1976; ID: 213.0173; 198205 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0173, Case 213.0173_pt.1, Case 213.0173_pt.2)
      Side A (July 26): Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet*, You Know More Than I Know, Guts, Waiting For the Man*, I Keep a Close Watch, The Jeweler -->, Gun -->, Pablo Picasso, Cable Hogue
      Side B: Babe What Ya Want Me To Do?/(July 27th) Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Know Darling, I Need You, Guts, Waiting For the Man, Gun -->, Pablo Picasso, Babe What You Want Me To Do?
      Containe Annotation: J.Cale-vocal, piano, guitar. M.Ronson- guitar. D. Byrne - guitar, B. vocal (27th), A. Lainer - guitar, piano, b. vocal (27th), * (26th P. Smith-Voice)
    - Television Demo, Eno & Williams 1974/ Cale with Lou, Patti, David Byrne- July 20 1976, Ocean Club, 1974/1976; ID: 213.0174; 198206 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0174, Case 213.0174_pt.1, Case 213.0174_pt.2)
      Side A (Television Demos): Prove It, Friction, Venus De Milo, Marquee Moon, Double Exposure, Fire Engine (live), Blank Generation (live)/ Heartbreakers Demo 1975: Love Comes in Spurts, I Wanna Be Loved, Blank Generation
      Side B (Cale): Ghost Story, Buffalo Ballet, You Know More Than I Know, Guts, Waiting For My Man, [Track Unknown] -->, Gun -->, Pablo Picasso, Babe What Ya Want Me To Do?
    - Lou Reed - Live Felt For, April 26, 1975, ID: 213.0175; 198207 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0175, Case 213.0175_pt.1, Case 213.0175_pt.2)
      Side A: Sweet Jane, I Wanna Be Black, Coney Island Baby, You Can Dance, I'm Waiting for My Man, Heroin, Berlin, Lady Ray
      Side B: Uptown Dirt, Walk on the Wild Side, Kicks, Complete This Story Now, Rock N Roll
      Container Annotation: Lou- guitar, vocal, Doug Yule- guitar, b. vocal
    - Ramones Live Max's Aug 6th 1976, August 1976; ID: 213.0176; 198208 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0176, Case 213.0176)
      Side A: Loudmouth, Beat on the Brats, Blitzkrieg Bop, Suzie is a Head Banger, Glad to See Ya Go, Gimmie Gimmie Shock Treatment, 53rd & 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don't Walk Around with You, I'm a Nazi baby, Today Ya Love
      Side B: Basement, Sniff Some Glue, Blitzkrieg Bop, I Don't Wanna Be a Pinhead No Nore, Chainsaw, Listen to My Heart, Baby Sitter, Commando, Oh Oh I Love Her So, Let's Dance, Walk Around, Nazi Baby, I'm Gonna Kill that Girl, Judy is a Punk, California Sun
    - Ramones CBGB May 15, 76/ LA Roxy August [] 76 -Radio-, May 1976, August 1976; ID: 213.0177; 198209 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0177, Case 213.0177)
      Side A: Basement, Sniff Glue, Blitz Bop, Swallow My Pride, Glad to See Ya Go, Chainsaw, Listen to My Heart, Babysitter, 53rd and 3rd, Havana Affair, Let's Dance, Judy
      Side B: Loudmouth, Beat on the Brats, Blitzkrieg Bop, Glad to See Ya Go, 53rd and 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Calif Sun, Judy, I Don't Wanna Walk, Nazi/ Void-oids - Down at the RnRoll Club
    - Ramones Live Max's. Aug 7 1976 stereo, PD & McKim. Feb 4th 1977 Mono dolby, 1976/1977; ID: 213.0178; 198210 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0178, Case 213.0178)
      Side A: Loudmouth, Brats, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Shock Treatment, 53rd and 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, Walk around with You, Nazi Baby, Today Ya Love, Tomorrow the World
      Side B: Loudmouth, Brat, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, ShockTreatment, 53rd and 3rd, Goodboy, Headbanger, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don't Wanna Walk around with You
    - Ramones - Max's October 8th 1976 (early) October 9th 1976 (late show), ID: 213.0179; 198211 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0179, Case 213.0179)
      Sides and B: Loudmouth, Brats, I Remember You, Glad to See You Go, Shock Treatment, Kill That Girl, Sniff Glue, 53rd and 3rd, Boyfriend, Judy, Havana Affair, Calif Sun, Walk Around, Nazi Baby -- Kill That Girl, Glad to See Ya Go, Gimmie Gimmie Shock Treatment, Commando, Sniff Glue, Suzy is a Head Banger, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don't Wanna Walk around with You, Nazi Baby, -- Chainsaw, Let's Dance
    - Ramones -all new- La Peste Hurrah July 4 1978/ My Father's Place July 5 1978, ID: 213.0180; 198212 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0180, Case 213.0180_pt.1, Case 213.0180_pt.2)
      Side A: Rockaway Beach, Lobotomy, Blitz Bop, I Don't Want You
      Side B: Glad to See Ya Go, Shock T, Somethin To Do, Wanted Every
    - Ramones Oct 30, 1977 CBGB early show/ late, a grape tape, ID: 213.0181; 198213 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0181, Case 213.0181_pt.1, Case 213.0181_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Loudmouth, Brats, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Teenage Lobotomy, Kill That Girl, Sheena, Rockaway Beach, Commando, Here Today- Gone Tomorrow, Surfin Bird, Cretin Hop, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Walk Around, Pinhead, 53rd and 3rd, Carbona, Nazi Baby, Basement, Sniff Glue
    - Ramones CBGB 1st set June 10th 77/ Nervous Rex -Max's Jan 15, 1978 Miriam Linna, 1977/1978; ID: 213.0182; 198214 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0182, Case 213.0182_pt.1, Case 213.0182_pt.2)
      (June 10th 77) Duplicators, Stop All Dancing, Dubrule 1250, Index, No Regrets Sort Of, Rachel in the Ruins, She's Not There, Leave Me Alone, Fun with Numbers
    - Ramones 6-9-77 CBGB 3 early 24 late, the Grape, 1977; ID: 213.0183; 198215 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0183, Case 213.0183_pt.1, Case 213.0183_pt.2)
      Side A: Swallow, Shock Treatment, I Don't Care, Loudmouth, Ramona, Blitz Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Teenage, Kill That Girl, Carbona Not Glue, Sheena is a Punk, Babysitter, Havana Affair, Pinhead, Sniff Glue, Nazi Baby
      Side B: Goodboy, Chainsaw, Calif Sun, 53rd & 3rd, Suzi, Love is the Drug, Tokyo Joe, This is Tomorrow, The In Crowd, A Hard Rain's Gonna Fall, Price of Love
    - Ramones LIVE July 13, 1976 My father's place, McKim, ID: 213.0184; 198216 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0184, Case 213.0184)
      Loudmouth
      General
      The final two minutes of track one are disrupted by tape malformation, which causes variable speed and stop/start. The glitches happen about every two seconds for this segment.
    - Ramones June 10th 76 Max's, 1976; ID: 213.0185; 198217 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0185, Case 213.0185_pt.1, Case 213.0185_pt.2)
      Side A: Loudmouth, Brats, Blitzkrieg Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Shock Treatment, 53rd & 3rd, Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, Calif Sun, Judy, Walk Away, Nazi Baby
      Side B: Basement, Sniff Glue, Glad to See Ya Go, Chainsaw, Listen to My Heart, Babysitter, Oh Oh I Love Her So, Commando, Let's Dance, Judy is a Punk, Walk Away, Nazi Baby-
    - Lenny K Xmas, CBGB xmas 79/ Mac, Cambodia Benefit Cooper Union, 1979; ID: 213.0186; 198218 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0186, Case 213.0186_pt.1, Case 213.0186_pt.2)
      Content: None
    - Modern Lovers- Live at the Kitchen NY March 1975/ Ramones- Live 9/14/75, ID: 213.0187; 198219 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0187, Case 213.0187_pt.1, Case 213.0187_pt.2)
      Modern Lovers: This Little Light of Mine, Rock Island Line, She's My Girlfriend, Cum Bi Ya, Goodninght Baby, No Need to Fear My Honest Dear, She Loves You Johnathan, Blue Suede Shoes, Don't Worry Baby, Born Too Late, Dreamland Girlfriend, New Teller (2nd time), Hi Friend We Still Love You, Roadrunner
      Tape Length: 120 minutes
    - Ramones May 15th 1976 CBGB late, Donk's rock concert/ "Ramones" LP, ID: 213.0188; 198220 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0188, Case 213.0188_pt.1, Case 213.0188_pt.2)
      Side A: (Ramones May 15 '76/Sets I & II) Sheena, Loudmouth, Brats, Blitz Bop, Heart, Calif Sun, Jusy, Glad to See Ya Go, Shock Treatment, Rockaway Beach, Commando-- Loudmouth, Beat on Brats, BlitzBop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, ShockTreatment
      Side B: (Ramones LP) Blitzkrieg Bop, Beat on the Brats, Judy is a Punk, I Wanna Be Your Boyfriend, Chain Saw, Now I Wanna Sniff Some Glue, Go Down to the Basement, [Lordern to] Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, 53rd & 3rd, Let's Dance, I Don't Wanna Walk Around with You, Nazi Baby- Today [Yal-ow]
      Container Annotation on Inside of Label for Side B ("Television" crossed out on physical tape for Side B) (Ramones Live May 15th CBGB Television): Fire Engine, Friction, Hard on Love, Blank Generation, Psychotic rxn, UFO, Marquee Moon, Prove it (cut)
    - Talking Heads/ Blondie/ Ramones LIVE at CBGB July 18th 1975, ID: 213.0189; 198221 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0189, Case 213.0189_pt.1, Case 213.0189_pt.2)
      Side A: Building on Fire, Artist's Only, Warning Sign, No Compassion. BLONDIE: In the Flesh, Moonlight Drive, Charlotte the Harlot, Platinum Blonde, Man Over Board.
      Side 2: RAMONES I Don't Wanna Go Down in the Basement, Beat on the Brats, Let's Dance, 53rd and 3rd, Havana Affair, Calif Sun, Judy is a Punk. [TALKING HEADS] I Don't Wanna, Girls Wanna Be with the Girls with Our Love, Psycho Killer, I'm Not in Llove. [RAMONES] I Don't Wanna Walk away with You, Nazi Baby, Today Ya Love.
      Container Annotation: David Byrne- guitar, vocals, Tina Wamouth- bass, Chris Frantz- drums
      Tape Length: 100 minutes
    - Television at Mother's Oct 1975/ Ramones July 18 1975 at CBGB's, ID: 213.0190; 198222 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0190, Case 213.0190)
      Side A: (Television at Mothers) Fire Engine, Judy Said, Marquee Moon, Iron Curtain, Friction, Breakin My Heart
      Side B: (Ramones) Basement, Beat on the Brat, Let's Dance, 53rd & 3rd, Havana Affair, Gonna Kill That Girl, California Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don't Wanna Walk away with You, Nazi
    - Ramones LIVE at Max's Aug 7, 1976 STEREO, ID: 213.0191; 198223 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0191, Case 213.0191_pt.1)
      Loudmouth, Beat on the Brat, Blitzkrieg Bop, I Remember You, Glad to See Ya Go, Gimmie Gimmie Shock Treatment, 53rd & 3rd, I Wanna Be Your Boyfriend, Havana Affair, Listen to My Heart, California Sun, Judy is a Punk, I Don't Wanna Walk around with You, Nazi
    - Tom Verlaine/ Bloomsbury Theatre 2nd show, undated; ID: 213.0192; 198224 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0192, Case 213.0192)
      Container Annotation: Both sides/ some other crap near end side A
    - Bruce Springsteen - Greetings from Asbury Park/Television Aug 8 1975 CBGB (copy), ID: 213.0193; 198225 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0193)
    - Television, Bottom Line 7/29/78 late show, 1978; ID: 213.0194; 198226 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0194, Case 213.0194_pt.1, Case 213.0194_pt.2)
      Side A: Fire Engine, Glory, Grip of Love, Foxhole, Dream's Dreamer, Aint That Worth Nothing, Friction, Prove it, Marquee Moon, Kingdom Come, Satisfaction, *Psychotic Reaction, *
      Side B (no denotation)
    - Television/ Z/ Syncopaticon 8/31/77, 1977; ID: 213.0195; 198227 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0195, Case 213.0195)
      Side A: Fire Engine, O Mi Amore, Adventure, Foxhole, Breakin in My Heart, I Don't Care
      Side B: Poor Circulation, Kingdom Come, Psychotic Reaction
      Tape Length: unknown
    - Tom Verlaine PEP Lounge Oct 13th 1981, ID: 213.0196; 198228 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0196, Case 213.0196_pt.1, Case 213.0196_pt.2)
      Sides A and B: Kingdom Come, Red Leaves, Souvenir of a Dream, Mile From You, Breakin in My Heart, Glory
    - Television Live at CBGB March 12, 1976 with the MONG, ID: 213.0197; 198229 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0197, Case 213.0197_pt.1, Case 213.0197_pt.2)
      Side A: Kingdom Come (contd), Fire Engine, Venus de Milo, Torn Curtain, Little Johnny Jewel, Friction, Prove it, Knockin on Heaven's Door, Marquee Moon
      Side B: Oh mi Amore, Poor Circulation, Elevation, Let Me Out, Grip of Love, I Don't Care
    - Television/ Talking Heads March 13, 1976 at the Kitchen, ID: 213.0198; 198230 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0198, Case 213.0198_pt.1, Case 213.0198_pt.2)
      Side A (Television March 12): Foxhole, Kingdom Come, Psychotic Reaction (encore). TALKING HEADS: Artists Only, First Week/Last Week, I'm Not in Love, Love is Like a Building on Fire, Who Is It?
      Side B: Thank You For Sending Me an Angel, Sugar on My Tongue, Warning Sign, Girls w/ Girls, Psycho Killer, In My Heart, I Wish You Wouldn't Say That, Stay Hungry, I Wanna Live, Tentative Decisions, No Compassion
      Container annotation: David Byrne- guitar, vocal, Chris Frantz- drums, vibes. Tina Weymouth-bass, occ guitar.
    - Television, Bottom Line June 11, 1978 early show, Pistols Jan 14 1978, ID: 213.0199; 198231 (Box 4, Media ID: 213.0199, Case 213.0199_pt.1, Case 213.0199_pt.2)
      Side A: Dreamer's Dreamer, Venus, Fristion, Pistols 1-14-78 part III